questionsDays

A hét napjai - Os dias da semana

numb: 1,
question: "Hét",
answer: "A. Semana",
options: [
		"A. Semana",
		"B. Dia",
		"C. Mês",
		"D. Ano"
]

numb: 2,
question: "Hétfő",
answer: "C. Segunda-feira",
options: [
		"A. Quinta-feira",
		"B. Quarta-feira",
		"C. Segunda-feira",
		"D. Sexta-feira"
]

numb: 3,
question: "Péntek",
answer: "A. Sexta-feira",
options: [
		"A. Sexta-feira",
		"B. Domingo",
		"C. Sábado",
		"D. Terça-feira"
]

numb: 4,
question: "Csütörtök",
answer: "D. Quinta-feira",
options: [
		"A. Sexta-feira",
		"B. Quarta-feira",
		"C. Terça-feira",
		"D. Quinta-feira"
]

numb: 5,
question: "Vasárnap",
answer: "A. Domingo",
options: [
		"A. Domingo",
		"B. Sábado",
		"C. Quinta-feira",
		"D. Quarta-feira"
]

numb: 6,
question: "Szerda",
answer: "C. Quarta-feira",
options: [
		"A. Sexta-feira",
		"B. Segunda-feira",
		"C. Quarta-feira",
		"D. Quinta-feira"
]

numb: 7,
question: "Nap",
answer: "A. Dia",
options: [
		"A. Dia",
		"B. Semana",
		"C. Mês",
		"D. Ano"
]

numb: 8,
question: "Szombat",
answer: "B. Sábado",
options: [
		"A. Semana",
		"B. Sábado",
		"C. Domingo",
		"D. Sexta-feira"
]

numb: 9,
question: "Kedd",
answer: "D. Terça-feira",
options: [
		"A. Quinta-feira",
		"B. Quarta-feira",
		"C. Segunda-feira",
		"D. Terça-feira"
]

numb: 10,
question: "Hétvége",
answer: "D. Final de semana",
options: [
		"A. Semana",
		"B. Os dias da semana",
		"C. Os meses do ano",
		"D. Final de semana"
]